{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Shéi" ,
      "answer": "谁"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lái",
      "answer": "来"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jièshào" ,
      "answer": "介绍"
    },
    {
      "question": "Míngzì",
      "answer": "名字"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhōngwén",
      "answer": "中文"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàba",
      "answer": "爸爸"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéxí",
      "answer": "学习"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xué",
      "answer": "学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhuānyè",
      "answer": "专业"
    },
    {
      "question": "Měishù",
      "answer": "美术"
    },
    {
      "question": "Měi",
      "answer": "美"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wénxué",
      "answer": "文学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xì",
      "answer": "系"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiānádà",
      "answer": "加拿大"
    },
    {
      "question": "Měiguó",
      "answer": "美国"
    }
  ]
}
